[{"answer": "Well, like I said before, capturing you was unintentional. The real reason I'm here is to catch a Goa'uld", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Dead-Man-Switch.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I hunt anyone of value", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I hunt anyone of value", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Dead-Man-Switch.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "His name is my friend'tar", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Almond bark. Barcalounger, Beetlejuice", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Dead-Man-Switch.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Well, if it was my friend, the door'd be opening, wouldn't it", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You're the linguist", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Dead-Man-Switch.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Well, try", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Well, try", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Dead-Man-Switch.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I said,", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Okay, well, I said,", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Dead-Man-Switch.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "He said", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yeah! How do you open this thing", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Dead-Man-Switch.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "How many combinations could there be", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "No. It's not true. And if you really hate the Goa'uld, you'd try to learn more about the Tok'ra", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Dead-Man-Switch.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Well, trying to defeat the Goa'uld is better than the alternative", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "If enough of the right allies work together, the task might not be so insurmountable", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Dead-Man-Switch.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You mean you won't. You know what I think? I think you care. And I don't think you like what you do nearly as much as you pretend to", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "It's a pretty noble thing you're doing", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Dead-Man-Switch.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I guess I never knew the Tok'ra were different, you know. So what made you betray Apophis", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You don't really think the Tok'ra and the humans have a chance of overthrowing the Goa'uld, do you", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Dead-Man-Switch.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I don't think so", "qsentId": 22}]